so Texas was hit with a storm I don't
even know week ago still flooded Florida
I believe is hit with and whatever
there's lots of chaos going on due to
global warming what oh Rico is about to
get a worse storm I think than what
Texas got and the positive side the
human story of people coming together
and rest meet each other I think they
learned from Hurricane Katrina that you
can't just leave things up to the
government they are human and failed and
don't necessarily have the resources to
respond to a natural disaster like they
probably would want to and that people
need them too there's a prison I believe
it was in Texas I was reading about that
the prisoners there are just living in
abhorrent conditions drinking toilet
water because they haven't been allowed
out of their cells their cells are
flooded they've been eating - sound
which is a day they get no hot food they
have a minute of their cells only know
this from front of the wives and last
feel good story but I feel like two
things one of which is we need a way to
keep tabs on prisoners and I don't mean
tabs like the state does I mean tabs
like to know that prisoners are okay
watching the which I realize is fiction
but based on some truth the orange is
the new black latest season of them in a
prison riot for the whole season and
these things can go on in prison and we
need to be able to have accountability
to know how prisoners are being treated
especially when they're being treated as
a quantity the other thing that I'm
feeling right now is that as tragic as
these storms are they're just gonna keep
happening until we do something about
how we're causing it there's gonna be
more and more frequent more devastating
and as much as we love to pull together
for people that are here in the West
with us and donate money that could only
happen so often we can't not
everyone can donate every forest fire
and every flood and every hurricane and
every tornado we just need to stop them
from happening we need to stop it's
insanity if not listening to scientists
and we're clear they not gonna listen to
the government nor should we because
they aren't necessarily trustworthy the
media is in it for profit
so we need to do it we need to collect
the data and figure out what needs to be
done and how much carbon is being
released by what it parts of the
industry and how can we do better and
that's a lot of what I want the global
cooperative to do and it just I don't
know I don't find it realized he puts
bloodying these hurricanes aren't about
me I'm here safe and Vancouver we have a
hazy day and I'm having difficulty
breathing outside and just low energy
because of forest fires that again are
directly affecting me their secondary
affecting me the smoke that drifts into
my city is affecting me and I can only
imagine losing my home worried about my
child not knowing you can't count on the
government not knowing what you're gonna
do is still having to pay rent when you
don't have somewhere to live and knowing
that this idea I have for a global
cooperative if I had started it five
years ago maybe I mean it would've
helped the actual flooding ends but we
would have had systems in place to help
a readily and to know that in the future
there's gonna be less and less storms
instead of more and more and better ways
of helping knowing where the nonprofit
money is going and how much is being
donated and where it's actually going
and what's the best use right if you're
trying to rehome people Hattie what's
the cheapest but most efficient way to
house people safely and with dignity
what's the best way to feed people to
get people clean water in this kind of
situation and there's just so many ways
that I see our
global or I know there's word for it
like our hive mind what together we all
have access to where when it's in anyone
who's part of the collective if they
know how to explain it they can explain
to everyone right that we share
knowledge and make up for the ways that
we ourselves lack knowledge so if you're
not a great interpersonal person if you
don't have great emotional intelligence
figuring out technology that can help
you because we're all deserving of love
and connection and if the current system
isn't working for people and it's not
those people who are definitely lonely
and disconnected I've been one of them
and figure you know how to get people
that information so there had disjointed
we were video I've talked about so many
different things but it's been five
minutes and I will be back on tomorrow
today is day 17 of my hundred day
challenge to put on a video every day
and I'm trying to share a little bit
about myself as opposed to just the
global cooperative idea um so you know
kind of how I got to it
well simultaneously I'm trying I'm
outlining the book I'm gonna be writing
the book to explain the global
cooperative all bit different pieces and
keep having conversations with friends
and family about it so that they ask
questions and points out what they think
I've left out and I usually haven't left
it don't I usually just haven't
mentioned it so it adds more fuel to me
so anyway hope everyone is staying safe
and like me out of the heat